<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shortcodes on TurboTides</title>
    <link>https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/tags/shortcodes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shortcodes on TurboTides</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/tags/shortcodes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Design, Simulation, and Optimization System OpTides</title>
      <link>https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/blog/20240925-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/blog/20240925-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On April 23, 2023, a day before the grand opening of the 8th &amp;ldquo;China Space Day,&amp;rdquo; a Fatigue/Crack Propagation Analysis Software Product Launch was held at the Global Roadshow Center of Zhong&amp;rsquo;an Chuanggu Science and Technology Park in Hefei High-tech Zone. This event was jointly organized by Anhui Jisuan Information Technology Co., Ltd. and Hefei Tai Ze Turbomachinery Technology Co., Ltd.&#xA;The launch aimed to showcase the SeniorCrack product, which represents a significant leap in digital R&amp;amp;D for high-end manufacturing and a crucial step in the transformation and upgrading of China&amp;rsquo;s manufacturing industry. The event invited leaders from relevant departments, industry experts, researchers from institutes, and professors from universities to engage in multidimensional and comprehensive discussions on the development of domestic CAE industrial software.&#xA;Anhui Jisuan Information Technology Co., Ltd. specializes in providing fatigue fracture simulation analysis software and full-stack solutions related to life testing, failure analysis, and engineering optimization for R&amp;amp;D and manufacturing enterprises. Hefei Tai Ze Turbomachinery Technology Co., Ltd., a national high-tech enterprise, focuses on the development of domestic CAE industrial software and related engineering technical services, covering six major business areas: turbomachinery technology, industrial software customization, fluid pipeline networks, structural strength, data science, and general CAE.&#xA;The launch was an important occasion to witness a historic moment and embrace future challenges and explorations&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made an Appearance at the Intelligent Oil and Gas Pipeline Conference</title>
      <link>https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/blog/20230714/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fanxgg.github.io/TurboTides/blog/20230714/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A problem has multiple solutions, among which there exists one or more optimal solutions.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;There is one or more measurable optimization &lt;strong&gt;objectives&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;There is one or more controllable &lt;strong&gt;optimization variables&lt;/strong&gt; that affect the objectives and constraints.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The problem has one or more &lt;strong&gt;constraints&lt;/strong&gt; that must be satisfied.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
